[
    {
        "Question": "What is Pylauncher?",
        "Answer Given": "The parallellines file consists of command-lines without the MPI job starter",
        "Score": 0.27364581823349,
        "Actual Answer": "a Python-based parametric job launcher, a utility for distributing and executing many small jobs in parallel"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do you load Pylauncher?",
        "Answer Given": "cmd-line\n$ module",
        "Score": 0.40129581093788147,
        "Actual Answer": "module load pylauncher"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What command installs Pylauncher?",
        "Answer Given": "ClassicLauncher",
        "Score": 0.23475387692451477,
        "Actual Answer": "module load pylauncher"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does Pylauncher do in an idev session?",
        "Answer Given": "creates a working directory with a name based on the SLURM job number",
        "Score": 0.6978831887245178,
        "Actual Answer": "creates a working directory with a name based on the SLURM job number"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Where is Pylauncher available on TACC?",
        "Answer Given": "all TACC systems",
        "Score": 0.2306841015815735,
        "Actual Answer": "on all TACC systems via the [Lmod modules system][TACCLMOD]"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the procees to invoke Pylauncher?",
        "Answer Given": "Slurm job script, or interactively within an idev session",
        "Score": 0.002375508425757289,
        "Actual Answer": "#SBATCH -N 5 # number of nodes you want to use"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many nodes will I need to use?",
        "Answer Given": "40",
        "Score": 0.0006351440097205341,
        "Actual Answer": "depends on how much work you have"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What are the names of the environment variables?",
        "Answer Given": "PYTHONPATH",
        "Score": 0.0023084257263690233,
        "Actual Answer": "TACC_PYLAUNCHER_DIR and PYTHONPATH"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How can I give each commandline more than one core for a multi-threaded program?",
        "Answer Given": "job-script\nlauncher",
        "Score": 0.13894513249397278,
        "Actual Answer": "launcher.ClassicLauncher(commandlines,cores4)"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How much time does it take for the system to output a tick message",
        "Answer Given": "The  tick message is output every half second",
        "Score": 0.3719596564769745,
        "Actual Answer": "every half second"
    }
]